MISSY MCGEE

Junior Web Developer

027 371 0732



melissaaemcgee@gmail.com



17 Kinloch Street, Christchurch, New Zealand



PERSONAL STATEMENT

Kia ora! I'm Missy, a people person with a positive attitude and determination to excel in any role that I take on. I exhibit a wide range of administrative experience. I am a well-organized and approachable individual who believes attention to detail and prioritization are essential to the success of any office I work in.

EDUCATION

Robertson College / Diploma

FEBRUARY 2022 - NOVEBMER 2022, BC, CANADA

Web Development Honours

Seneca College / Diploma

SEPTEMBER 2008- JUNE 2010, ONT. CANADA

Early Childhood Education Honours

REFERENCES

JODY-LYNN COX

CAO Village of Warfield MONTH 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022, WARFIELD, CANADA

JEANETTE EINARSON

Senior Accountant Supervisor SEPTEMBER 2018- JULY 2019, PEMBERTON, CANADA

EXPERIENCE

Village of Warfield / Senior Administrative Assistant JANUARY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022, WARFIELD, CANADA

- Key liaison for contractors and suppliers during extensive office renovation and staff relocation.
- Research and order supplies for renovation including office equipment and service hook-ups while maintaining the daily function of the office.
- Department liaison for vacation, event and conference co-ordination and booking.
- Weekly payroll processing, management, and distribution.
- Creation of Council Agenda, meeting assembly, and minute taking.

School District 20 Kootenay Columbia / ECE

SEPTEMBER 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2020, ROSSLAND, CANADA

- Supervise and teach students in small groups or one on one in classrooms, schoolyards and on field trips.
- Ensure students have adequate supplies to enhance their learning and development.
- Organize lessons and activities to engage students individually and within peer groups.

Village of Pemberton / Finance Administrative Assistant SEPTEMBER 2018 – JULY 2019, PREMBERTON, CANADA

- Office duties including greeting guests, ordering supplies, and maintaining cleanliness of office.
- Read and analyse incoming memos, submissions, and reports to determine significance and distribution.
- Greet customers, attend to any queries, receive payments and daily cash reconciliation.

SKILLS

- Positive and resilient
- Organization and initiative
- Professional and courteous
- Written and verbal communication